<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Deep learning</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Deep learning</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us-vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:49:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2. Linear Regression</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:49:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Tab of content Tab of content 1. Introduction 2. Mathematical modeling 2.1 Mathematical analysis 2.2 Loss Function 2.3multiple linear regression 3. Methods 3.1 Closed-Form Solution 3.2 Gradient descent 4. Numerical studies 1. Introduction Linear regression is a Supervised Learning algorithm. It&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to find relationship between the independent variable and a dependent variable to predict the outcome of the new feature. Linear regression models are often used to predict the value of a continuous number such as salary, house price, age,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 thì trong tiếng anh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/sauthitrongtienganh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/sauthitrongtienganh/</guid>
      <description>Tab of content 1. Thì hiện tại đơn 1.1 Cách Thành Lập. 1.2 Cách Dùng Chính. 1.3 CÁCH THÊM S/ES. 2. HIỆN TẠI TIẾP DIỄN. table content 1. HIỆN TẠI ĐƠN (Present Simple Tense) 1.1 Cách thành lập. 1.2 Cách dùng chính Thì hiện tại đơn dùng để diễn tả: Một thói quen hoặc 1 hành động lập đi lặp lại. Trong câu thường có các trạng từ như: always, open ,usually, somethimes, seldom, rarely, every day/month, &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, my name’s Thanh Hoai. I&#39;m currently studying at the SaiGon Teachnology University.&#xD;I’m a sophomore at University of Information Technology. I really like computer science. I&#39;m very happy to be&#xD;here to day. I want to share my understanding of Artificial Intelligence with everyone to convey:&#xD;Người vá trời lấp bể Kẻ đắp luỹ xây thành Ta chỉ là chiếc lá Việc của mình là xanh&#xA;Source: Trái tim người lính (thơ), Nguyễn Sĩ Đại, NXB Thanh niên.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
