<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Deep learning</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Deep learning</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us-vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3. K-Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/k-nearest_neighbors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/k-nearest_neighbors/</guid>
      <description>Tab of content Tab of content 1. Introduction 2. Mathematical modeling 3. Code example on iris flower dataset 1. Introduction the K-Nearest Neighbors (KNN) is a supervised machine learning method employed to tackle classification and regression problems. When training, it doesn’t learn anything from the data but mechanically memorizes it. Therefore, this algorithm is called Lazy Learning. With KNN in classification problems, the label of a new data point is inferred from its K nearest data points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Linear Regression</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:49:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Tab of content Tab of content 1. Introduction 2. Mathematical modeling 2.1 Mathematical analysis 2.2 Loss Function 2.3multiple linear regression 3. Methods 3.1 Closed-Form Solution 3.2 Gradient descent 4. Numerical studies 1. Introduction Linear regression is a Supervised Learning algorithm. It&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to find relationship between the independent variable and a dependent variable to predict the outcome of the new feature. Linear regression models are often used to predict the value of a continuous number such as salary, house price, age,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, my name’s Thanh Hoai. I&#39;m currently studying at the SaiGon Teachnology University.&#xD;I’m a sophomore at University of Information Technology. I really like computer science. I&#39;m very happy to be&#xD;here to day. I want to share my understanding of Artificial Intelligence with everyone to convey:&#xD;Người vá trời lấp bể Kẻ đắp luỹ xây thành Ta chỉ là chiếc lá Việc của mình là xanh&#xA;Source: Trái tim người lính (thơ), Nguyễn Sĩ Đại, NXB Thanh niên.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
